Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
Legenda cedida pelo tradutor dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
Hi. My young master bastard.
Olá. Meu jovem mestre bastardo.
Hey, film this.
Ei, filme isso.
Our young master.
O nosso jovem mestre.
Are you happy?
Está feliz?
-You are stupid. -Yeah?
-Você é estúpido. -É?
-You want to die? -Die?
-Quer morrer? -Morrer?
Wake up, young master.
Acorde, jovem mestre.
-Hey. -Hey. Let go.
-Olá. -Olá. Solte.
I was a boxer. Bring it on.
Eu era pugilista. Vamos lá.
Bring it on.
Pode vir.
Happy?
Feliz?
I don't care whether you spend this money on gambling or on drugs.
Não me interessa se gasta esse dinheiro em jogos de azar ou em drogas.
What I care about is
O que me importa é
how you brought this money into this country without any trouble.
como trouxe esse dinheiro para este país sem qualquer problema.
This is my first time. You have to trust me.
É a minha primeira vez. Tens que confiar em mim.
Are you trying to slip out of this by yourself?
Está a tentar sair dessa sozinho?
I'm doing this because I'm a newbie.
Estou a fazer isto porque sou novato.
-I never-- -Sir.
-Eu nunca-- -Senhor.
I need you to take a look at this.
Preciso que dê uma vista de olhos nisso.
Here's the video of Rising Airlines' love child.
Eis o vídeo do filho ilegível da Rising Airlines.
Me? What about me? What?
Eu? E eu? O quê?
RISING AIRLINES' LOVE CHILD
O FILHO DO AMOR DA RISING AIRLINES
Check his left shoulder.
Verifique o seu ombro esquerdo.
A gun?
Uma arma?
Who are you?
Quem és tu?
Hey, show me the video.
Ei, mostra-me o vídeo.
If you're going to scam me, at least do it right.
Se me vai dar um golpe, pelo menos faça-o bem.
What?
O quê?
It's on the other side! I swear!
É do outro lado! Juro!
That's a mirror reflection!
Isto é um reflexo no espelho!
For Christ's sake! I told you. It's on the right shoulder.
Por amor de Deus! Eu disse-te. É no ombro direito.
Jeez, a gun?
Uau, uma arma?
EPISODE 2
EPISÓDIO 2
Just sit tight and answer my calls.
Basta ficar quieto e atender as minhas ligações.
I could have you locked up for smuggling cash, overseas gambling,
Poderia prendê-lo por contrabando de dinheiro, jogo no estrangeiro,
and even drugs.
e até drogas.
Would you rather be locked up in the Philippines or Korea?
Preferia ficar preso nas Filipinas ou na Coreia?
See you in Seoul.
Vemo-nos em Seul.
Yes, sir.
Sim, senhor.
Okay! He took the bait.
Certo! Ele mordeu o isco.
Jeon Tae-su's not easy as they said.
Jeon Tae-su não é fácil como disseram.
I swear I almost peed my pants.
Juro que quase fiz chichi nas calças.
If you'd listened to me and just played the pilot,
Se me tivesse ouvido e apenas tocado o piloto,
that all could've been avoided.
que tudo poderia ter sido evitado.
-Right? -What?
-Certo? -O quê?
Good job.
Bom trabalho.
Yi-rang, why did you take that?
Yi-rang, porque é que tirou isso?
That's a stimulant!
Isto é um estimulante!
Spit it out!
Desembucha!
Spit it out already!
Desembucha logo!
Spit it out, Yi-rang!
Desembucha, Yi-rang!
Yi-rang!
Yi-tocou!
Come on. I'm not stupid enough to take that.
Vamos lá. Eu não sou burro o suficiente para aceitar isto.
Seriously, you always crack me up.
A sério, fazes-me sempre rir.
-Jeez! -Let's go.
-Uau! -Vamos.
Just get in the car.
Basta entrar no carro.
-You're making the pain worse. -Good job. Now, lean on me.
-Está a piorar a dor. -Bom trabalho. Agora, apoie-se em mim.
Check when he was in the Philippines and his alibi at the casino and the club.
Verifique quando esteve nas Filipinas e o seu álibi no casino e no clube.
Yes, sir.
Sim, senhor.
It's me. I need you to look into something.
Sou eu. Preciso que investigue uma coisa.
Closely mark him to see if he's the love child of Rising Airlines.
Marque-o com atenção para ver se é filho ilegítimo da Rising Airlines.
If anything suspicious comes up, report it immediately.
Se surgir algo suspeito, denuncie imediatamente.
Yes, sir.
Sim, senhor.
We're home.
Estamos em casa.
Nangrang, be careful.
Nangrang, tenha cuidado.
Come on, Jeje. One, two.
Vamos, Jeje. Um, dois.
Jeje, be careful. Slow down.
Jeje, cuidado. Devagar.
Oh, my babies. You're home.
Ah, os meus bebés. Vocês chegaram a casa.
Goodness.
Bondade.
It's Mommy and Daddy.
É a mamã e o papá.
Say you're home.
Digamos que está em casa.
My babies refuse to go outside
Os meus bebés se recusam a sair
without you, Mr. Myung.
sem si, Sr. Myung.
No need to call me Mr. Myung.
Não precisa de me tratar por Sr. Myung.
If you need me to walk them, just give me a call.
Se precisar que os leve a passear, é só ligar-me.
Here.
Aqui.
Thank you for your work.
Obrigado pelo seu trabalho.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
Oh, hold on.
Ah, espere um pouco.
Thank you so much.
Muito obrigada.
Oh wow. Goodness. Thank you.
Uau! Uau! Obrigada.
-No problem. -Thanks for your work.
-Não há problema. -Obrigado pelo seu trabalho.
Goodbye.
Adeus.
It's a pleasure to see you here in Seoul.
É um prazer vê-lo aqui em Seul.
Let's cut to the chase. Bring the package.
Vamos diretos ao ponto. Traga o pacote.
SAND FOUNDATION
FUNDAÇÃO DE AREIA
Take it to the Philippines
Leve para as Filipinas
and hand it off to our guy in the agreed spot.
e entregá-lo ao nosso rapaz no local combinado.
May I ask what's inside that…
Posso perguntar o que está dentro disto…
Sorry.
Desculpa.
What do you think matters the most in life?
O que acha que é mais importante na vida?
Well, obviously, that's mon--
Bem, obviamente, é isso mesmo...
-It's trust. -Trust.
-É confiança. -Confiança.
Since I'm trusting you with the job, there are rules you need to follow.
Já que lhe estou a confiar o trabalho, há regras que precisa de seguir.
Don't open the package under any circumstances.
Não abra a embalagem em circunstância alguma.
And no matter what happens,
E não importa o que aconteça,
do not mention my name.
não mencione o meu nome.
If you break these rules…
Se quebrar estas regras…
If we do…
Se fizermos…
Use your imagination. What do you think would happen?
Use a sua imaginação. O que achas que aconteceria?
Are you sure we'll be okay?
Tem a certeza de que ficaremos bem?
We do have a plan in place, don't we?
Nós temos um plano em prática, não é?
Please tell me that we do.
Por favor, diga-me que sim.
Not telling you.
Não te vou contar.
What? How can you be joking…
O quê? Como pode estar a brincar...
Hey!
Olá!
If I ask you a question, I expect an answer.
Se lhe fizer uma pergunta, espero uma resposta.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ah, desculpe.
I'm sure you won't die.
Tenho a certeza de que não vai morrer.
So typical. You always have everything your way.
Tão típico. Faz sempre tudo do seu jeito.
Maybe you should try using your brain like me.
Talvez devesse tentar usar o seu cérebro como eu.
How dare you stare at me with those round eyes?
Como se atreve a encarar-me com esses olhos redondos?
Do you want me to make them square? Or perhaps a triangle shape?
Quer que eu os faça quadrados? Ou talvez triangulares?
See! There it is! You keep talking back!
Viu! Aí está! Você continua a responder!
Do you really want to see me lose my temper?
Quer mesmo ver-me perder a paciência?
Having fun?
Está a divertir-se?
Enjoy it while you can.
Aproveite enquanto pode.
It's just an act. Let's go.
É apenas uma encenação. Vamos lá.
Come on. It's a great deal.
Vamos lá. É um ótimo negócio.
-Is it 300 per night? -It's 800…
-São 300 por noite? -São 800…
Please give us a discount.
Por favor, dê-nos um desconto.
What are you staring at?
O que está a olhar?
Just thinking about the old days.
Só a pensar nos velhos tempos.
Back at Sunyuldo Island, where we first met.
De volta à Ilha Sunyuldo, onde nos conhecemos.
-Make it 700. -It's 800.
-Faça 700. -São 800.
The place is near.
O local é próximo.
-We don't have that much. -Make it 700.
-Não temos tanto. -Faça 700.
WELCOME GU-HO'S INN
BEM-VINDO À POUSADA GU-HO
Did you make a reservation for tonight?
Fez uma reserva para esta noite?
Yes, that's right.
Sim, está certo.
I see. Hello.
Eu vejo. Olá.
So what do you say?
Então o que diz?
-Where is it anyway? -Just around there.
-Onde fica? -É mesmo ali.
Right. It does feel familiar.
Certo. Parece mesmo familiar.
Peaceful, simple, and quiet.
Pacífico, simples e tranquilo.
You used to be just like him.
Você costumava ser igual a ele.
Yeah, I was just like him.
Sim, eu era exatamente como ele.
Although things have changed a lot,
Embora as coisas tenham mudado muito,
maybe we can go back one day.
talvez possamos voltar um dia.
Are you sleeping?
Você está a dormir?
You're the one who started this conversation.
Foi você que iniciou esta conversa.
What the heck?
Que raio?
Is he still knocked out?
Ele ainda está desmaiado?
I told you to go easy on the gas. We don't have much time.
Eu disse-lhe para ir com calma no acelerador. Não temos muito tempo.
I'm sorry.
Lamento.
Where's the girl? Let's check on her.
Onde está a garota? Vamos dar uma vista de olhos nela.
What the heck?
Que raio?
Damn.
Maldito.
Jeez! You scared me! Who are you?
Uau! Você assustou-me! Quem é você?
Who do you think? I'm the one who kidnapped you.
Quem acha que foi? Fui eu que te raptei.
Kidnap?
Sequestro?
-You know Jeon Tae-su, right? -Yes.
-Conheces o Jeon Tae-su, certo? -Sim.
I mean, no.
Quer dizer, não.
I used to work with him back in the day, but there was a small misunderstanding.
Eu trabalhava com ele antigamente, mas houve um pequeno mal-entendido.
So unfortunately, he had my internal organs rearranged.
Depois, infelizmente, ele reorganizou os meus órgãos internos.
See, I'm not the kind of guy who can sleep at night when I owe others.
Repare, não sou o tipo de rapaz que consegue dormir à noite quando está em dívida para com os outros.
So I plan to pay him back.
Assim pretendo retribuir.
Is this your bag?
Essa é a sua mala?
That man is still up to his old tricks.
Aquele homem ainda continua com os seus velhos truques.
If you had shown up at the drop point with this package,
Se tivesse aparecido no ponto de entrega com este pacote,
you would've been picked up by the police and thrown into some filthy cell for days.
teria sido apanhado pela polícia e atirado para alguma cela imunda durante dias.
That's what he does to test your loyalty. To see if you'll rat him out or not.
É isso que ele faz para testar a sua lealdade. Para ver se o vai denunciar ou não.
I don't know why that's in my bag.
Não sei porque é que isto está na minha bolsa.
I have nothing to do with any of this. You have to believe me.
Não tenho nada a ver com isso. Tens que acreditar em mim.
Look, lady.
Olha, menina.
Drop the lousy act.
Pare de agir assim.
I'm taking this to the Narcotics Division in Korea,
Vou levar isto para a Divisão de Narcóticos na Coreia,
and I'm going to need you to testify.
e vou precisar que testemunhe.
I have to get out of here.
Tenho de sair daqui.
Yi-rang, hang in there.
Yi-rang, aguente-se.
I'll go and get the cops myself.
Eu próprio irei chamar a polícia.
Those scumbags.
Esses canalhas.
Look at that.
Olha para isto.
How are you guys doing?
Como estão?
Don't come this way.
Não venha por aqui.
-No! Stop! -What's this idiot doing?
-Não! Pare! -O que é que este idiota está a fazer?
-Wait. Stay! -You can't get out of here.
-Espere. Fique! -Não pode sair daqui.
Gu-ho.
Gu-ho.
Oh, I know. I get it.
Ah, já sei. Eu compreendo.
Chairman Jeon told you to keep your mouth shut.
O presidente Jeon disse- lhe para ficar de boca fechada.
But guess what?
Mas adivinhem?
You know what happens when you fail to carry out his order?
Sabe o que acontece quando não cumpre a ordem dele?
Is that so?
É assim mesmo?
Oh, fuck. I…
Ah, merda. Eu…
Horrible, right?
Horrível, certo?
The young man you came with tried something cute.
O rapaz com quem vieste tentou algo fofo.
Awful, right?
Horrível, certo?
Even if you two make it out of here, the chairman's still going to kill you.
Mesmo que consigam sair os dois daqui, o presidente vai matar-vos na mesma.
So? Feeling a bit more cooperative now?
E aí? Está a sentir-se um pouco mais cooperante agora?
Or do you want your friend to wear mittens for the rest of his life?
Ou quer que o seu amigo use luvas para o resto da vida?
Please have mercy.
Por favor, tenha misericórdia.
-What? -Not on me…
-O quê? -Não em mim…
but my friend.
mas meu amigo.
Make it his ring finger instead of his middle finger.
Coloque-o no dedo anelar em vez do dedo médio.
At the very least, allow him to make a living.
No mínimo, permita que ele ganhe a vida.
Please, I beg you.
Por favor, eu imploro.
The lady next door asked me
A senhora da porta ao lado perguntou-me
to chop your ring finger off instead of your middle finger.
cortar o seu dedo anelar em vez do dedo médio.
Why?
Porquê?
I'm only going to take your pinky.
Só vou buscar o teu mindinho.
You'll lose your wrist if you move. Stay still.
Perderá o pulso se se mexer. Fique parado.
Clench your teeth. It's going to hurt a bit.
Cerre os dentes. Vai doer um pouco.
What was that?
O que é que foi aquilo?
I told you not to move.
Eu disse-lhe para não se mexer.
Stay still.
Fique parado.
I'll cut her finger instead.
Em vez disso, vou cortar-lhe o dedo.
No, wait!
Não, espere!
Hold on.
Espera.
Wait. I'll do it.
Espere. Eu farei isso.
Keep your finger straight.
Mantenha o dedo direito.
Put it here. I'll just cut up to here.
Coloque aqui. Vou cortar até aqui.
That's all I'll take.
É tudo o que vou levar.
Stay still.
Fique parado.
What now?
E agora?
Good job.
Bom trabalho.
My finger.
O meu dedo.
I still have it.
Eu ainda o tenho.
It's still there.
Ainda está lá.
Are you okay?
Está bem?
Chairman Jeon?
Presidente Jeon?
Chairman Jeon.
Presidente Jeon.
You're really in the mood for this right now?
Está realmente com vontade disso agora?
Do you have any idea what I went through?
Tem alguma ideia do que passei?
And you asked him to take my ring finger? Are you kidding me?
E pediu-lhe para me tirar o dedo anelar? Tás a brincar?
Gu-ho, why do you always see just one side of things?
Gu-ho, porque é que vês sempre apenas um lado das coisas?
I do see more than one side of things.
Vejo mais do que um lado das coisas.
The man who kidnapped us.
O homem que nos raptou.
He said it with his own mouth that he had gone through the same thing.
Disse com a sua própria boca que tinha passado pela mesma coisa.
But he had all five fingers on his hand.
Mas tinha os cinco dedos da mão.
He was just bluffing about chopping fingers off.
Ele estava apenas a fazer bluff sobre cortar dedos.
It's all a set-up.
É tudo uma armação.
I bet you Jeon Tae-su heard every word we said.
Aposto que Jeon Tae-su ouviu cada palavra que dissemos.
That man is still up to his old tricks.
Aquele homem ainda continua com os seus velhos truques.
Anyway, thanks to your heartfelt performance today,
De qualquer forma, graças à sua apresentação sincera de hoje,
I'm pretty sure Jeon Tae-su's fully convinced now.
Tenho a certeza de que Jeon Tae-su está totalmente convencido agora.
Lucky day for us.
Dia de sorte para nós.
I'm being completely serious right now.
Estou a falar muito a sério agora.
I think Jeon Tae-su is
Eu acho que o Jeon Tae-su é
way more caring than you are.
muito mais atencioso do que você.
For one, he hugged me. Okay?
Primeiro, abraçou-me. Certo?
He comforted me. Right?
Ele confortou-me. Certo?
What else?
O que mais?
-Gu-ho. -What?
-Gu-ho. -O quê?
Have you forgotten about James?
Esqueceu-se do James?
Are you a piece of trash?
É um pedaço de lixo?
Jeon Tae-su, that scum of the earth.
Jeon Tae-su, essa escumalha da terra.
That's right.
Isso mesmo.
When is Jeon Tae-su going to reach us?
Quando é que Jeon Tae-su vai chegar até nós?
That scumbag.
Aquele canalha.
Just wait until he calls me…
Espere só até ele me ligar…
Salute. Thank you, sir.
Saudação. Obrigado, senhor.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE FINANCIAL INVESTIGATION
GABINETE DO PROCURADOR DO DISTRITO CENTRAL DE SEUL INVESTIGAÇÃO FINANCEIRA
SAND FOUNDATION FINANCIAL STATEMENT NOTICE OF TAX AUDIT COMMENCEMENT
DEMONSTRAÇÃO FINANCEIRA DA FUNDAÇÃO SAND AVISO DE INÍCIO DE AUDITORIA FISCAL
THIS IS TO NOTIFY YOU THAT A TAX AUDIT WILL BE CONDUCTED
ISTO É PARA NOTIFICÁ- LO QUE SERÁ REALIZADA UMA AUDITORIA FISCAL
This much evidence could lead to a search warrant within a month.
Tantas provas podem levar a um mandado de busca no prazo de um mês.
I need to push the timeline forward.
Preciso de adiantar o cronograma.
I will keep that in mind.
Vou ter isso em mente.
What do you want me to do about the two? Should I keep digging?
O que é que quer que eu faça com os dois? Devo continuar a cavar?
No, there's no need for that.
Não, não há necessidade disso.
How much is all this?
Quanto custa tudo isto?
It's 50 billion won.
São 50 mil milhões de wons.
Fifty billion won?
Cinquenta mil milhões de won?
Everything needs to be moved to my summer house in Manila by next Friday.
Tudo precisa de ser levado para a minha casa de verão em Manila até à próxima sexta-feira.
The amount is much larger than we expected,
O valor é muito superior ao que esperávamos,
so our current methods won't--
então os nossos métodos actuais não irão--
Are you saying no?
Está a dizer não?
Sir, with that amount,
Senhor, com essa quantia,
isn't it better to open a shell company in the Bahamas
não seria melhor abrir uma empresa de fachada nas Bahamas
and send it to that location?
e enviá-lo para esse local?
You think I didn't look into that?
Acha que eu não pesquisei sobre isso?
I'm sure you did, sir.
Tenho a certeza que sim, senhor.
Stop spinning that worthless brain of yours and find a way.
Pare de rodar esse seu cérebro inútil e arranje um caminho.
That's why I kept you alive.
É por isso que o mantive vivo.
Well, there is one way.
Bem, há uma maneira.
Good. And that is?
Bom. E é?
To reduce the time it takes to board during vacation season,
Para reduzir o tempo de embarque durante a época de férias,
they opened a new lane that allows passengers
abriram uma nova faixa que permite aos passageiros
to skip taking out their laptops from their luggage.
para não tirarem os computadores portáteis da bagagem.
We can fool the X-ray
Podemos enganar o raio X
by placing a shielding device in our luggage.
colocando um dispositivo de proteção na nossa bagagem.
This device will absorb radiation and block X-rays,
Este dispositivo irá absorver a radiação e bloquear os raios X,
which will allow it to slip through security.
o que lhe permitirá passar pela segurança.
All right.
Tudo bem.
Shall we get started?
Vamos começar?
Yes.
Sim.
Gosh. What's wrong with this dog?
Nossa. O que há de errado com este cão?
Go away.
Vai-te embora.
Hey, get away from me. Come on.
Ei, sai de perto de mim. Vamos.
-What-- -You need to come with us.
-O quê-- -Precisa de vir connosco.
Where are you taking me?
Para onde me está a levar?
Let go! Don't touch me!
Solte-me! Não me toque!
Stay still.
Fique parado.
I'm sorry.
Lamento.
What happened?
O que aconteceu?
Why was that dog all over that bag?
Porque é que aquele cão estava em cima daquela sacola?
Due to recent issues with cash smuggling,
Devido a problemas recentes com o contrabando de dinheiro,
a cash-sniffing dog was deployed as of yesterday.
um cão farejador de dinheiro foi ontem destacado.
I should've informed you about this in advance. I'm sorry.
Eu devia ter-te avisado sobre isso antes. Peço desculpa.
What are you going to do about the money?
O que vai fazer com o dinheiro?
Do you know how much was in there? That was one billion won!
Sabe quanto tinha lá dentro? Era um bilião de wons!
The love child is back.
O filho ilegível está de volta.
Bring him to me.
Traga-mo.
Hey. Ouch. Hold on.
Ei. Ai. Espere aí.
-Where's the bag? -What?
-Onde está a mala? -O quê?
Well, my father got me out…
Bem, o meu pai tirou-me de lá…
I mean, he pulled some strings.
Quer dizer, mexeu uns cordelinhos.
About the money, that needs to be investigated…
Sobre o dinheiro, isso tem de ser investigado…
If anything happens to my money,
Se alguma coisa acontecer ao meu dinheiro,
I'll cut you open and sell whatever's worth anything
Vou abrir-te e vender tudo o que vale alguma coisa
down to the bones.
até aos ossos.
-What? -Take them both.
-O quê? -Leve os dois.
Would you like a flyer?
Gostaria de um folheto?
Darn it.
Droga.
Sir, this is it.
Senhor, é isto.
All you need to do is focus on your responsibilities.
Tudo o que tem de fazer é concentrar-se nas suas responsabilidades.
Are you out of your mind?
Está louco?
Sir, think about it.
Senhor, pense nisso.
What does the Sand Foundation do?
O que faz a Sand Foundation?
Protect children, respond to disasters, and fight poverty.
Proteja as crianças, responda a catástrofes e combata a pobreza.
What are you trying to pull here?
O que está a tentar fazer aqui?
Basically…
Basicamente…
We promote the Sand Foundation's spirit of giving
Promovemos o espírito de doação da Sand Foundation
on a global scale through a massive donation campaign.
à escala global através de uma campanha massiva de donativos.
Which means we charter a private flight
O que significa que fretamos um voo privado
to send relief supplies overseas.
para enviar mantimentos de socorro para o exterior.
FILL A RELIEF BOX SPREAD WARMTH ACROSS THE WORLD
ENCHA UMA CAIXA DE ALÍVIO ESPALHE CALOR PELO MUNDO
What are you saying?
O que está a dizer?
We'll fill it with clothes, medicine, and relief supplies.
Vamos enchê-lo com roupas, medicamentos e mantimentos de emergência.
If we split the bags of cash in those boxes,
Se dividirmos os sacos de dinheiro por estas caixas,
no one will suspect anything?
ninguém vai desconfiar de nada?
Leave the chartered plane to me, sir.
Deixe o avião fretado comigo, senhor.
You know, I have my ways, right?
Sabe, eu tenho os meus métodos, certo?
Ms. Kim.
ª Kim.
That's impressive.
Isso é impressionante.
Good job.
Bom trabalho.
Jeez.
Nossa.
What was that for?
Para que foi?
My blood sugar's dropping.
O meu nível de açúcar no sangue está a cair.
Jeon Tae-su sure is intense, right?
Jeon Tae-su é mesmo intenso, certo?
He said he'd sell whatever's worth anything down to the bones. Jeez.
Disse que venderia qualquer coisa que valesse a pena, até aos ossos. Nossa.
You did well out there, Gu-ho. Eat as much as you want.
Fizeste bem, Gu-ho. Coma à vontade.
Hey!
Olá!
This pungent and funky cheese scent.
Este aroma pungente e funky de queijo.
There's no way a dog could resist that.
Não há como um cão resistir a isto.
Your timing was impeccable.
O seu timing foi impecável.
-Go away. What-- -You need to come with us.
-Vá-se embora. O quê... -Precisa de vir connosco.
Are you serious?
Está a falar sério?
Why did you go the hard way and make things so complicated?
Porque é que fez o que era difícil e complicou tanto as coisas?
We could've just chartered a plane from the start.
Podíamos ter fretado um avião desde o início.
Here's the thing.
A questão é a seguinte.
I had to show Jeon Tae-su that
Eu tinha que mostrar isto a Jeon Tae-su
moving the money using our current method was not an option.
movimentar o dinheiro utilizando o nosso método atual não era uma opção.
For that to happen,
Para que isso aconteça,
he had to witness you getting caught.
ele teve de testemunhar você a ser apanhado.
That's how it works.
É assim que funciona.
Once suspicion fades, it gives way to trust.
Quando a suspeita desaparece, dá lugar à confiança.
If we had brought up the chartered plane from the start,
Se tivéssemos mencionado o avião fretado desde o início,
he wouldn't have bought into the idea.
não teria acreditado na ideia.
What? Did you fall for me again?
O quê? Apaixonou-se por mim de novo?
Oh, come on.
Ah, vamos lá.
Am I really that pretty? Jeez.
Serei mesmo tão bonita assim? Nossa.
I have to admit, the shielding device that bypasses security was quite clever.
Tenho de admitir, o dispositivo de blindagem que contorna a segurança foi bastante inteligente.
Thanks.
Obrigado.
Seriously, who would've guessed this was all staged and set up beforehand?
A sério, quem diria que tudo isto foi encenado e montado de antemão?
That's how people are.
É assim que as pessoas são.
They only believe what they can see with their own eyes.
Só acreditam no que veem com os seus próprios olhos.
They have no clue how tight aviation security is.
Não têm ideia de quão rigorosa é a segurança da aviação.
Gosh, Yi-rang.
Uau, Yi-rang.
Seriously, how do you always come up with these kinds of ideas?
A sério, como é que tem sempre este tipo de ideia?
You were born to do this.
Você nasceu para o fazer.
It'd be a shame to let this talent go to waste.
Seria uma pena desperdiçar este talento.
Jeez.
Nossa.
Now, Gu-ho.
Agora, Gu-ho.
What's next?
O que vem a seguir?
I just received word that he'll be arriving soon.
Acabei de receber a notícia de que chegará em breve.
Long time no see.
Há quanto tempo.
Excuse me?
Desculpa?
I was supposed to meet you with the chairman,
Eu deveria encontrá-lo com o presidente,
but I've been too busy to reach out.
mas tenho estado demasiado ocupado para entrar em contacto.
So, how exactly do we know…
Então, como sabemos exatamente…
Don't be a stranger. Come on.
Não seja um estranho. Vamos lá.
Card.
Cartão.
Let's talk upstairs. Come on.
Vamos conversar lá em cima. Vamos.
-Okay. -All right.
-Ok. -Tudo bem.
SAND FOUNDATION CHIEF FINANCIAL OFFICER GO HO-JIN
DIRECTOR FINANCEIRO DA FUNDAÇÃO SAND, GO HO-JIN
If things go according to plan,
Se as coisas correrem como planeado,
the Sand Foundation will fully back the fundings.
a Sand Foundation apoiará integralmente os financiamentos.
Oh, of course. It's for a good cause.
Ah, claro. É por uma boa causa.
Naturally, we'll do everything to support you.
Naturalmente, tudo faremos para o apoiar.
If you need anything besides the flight--
Se precisar de alguma coisa para além do voo...
One more thing.
Mais uma coisa.
No one outside of these four walls must know about our meeting today.
Ninguém fora destas quatro paredes deve saber da nossa reunião de hoje.
Don't even tell the chairman about this.
Nem conte isso ao presidente.
Since we're a charitable foundation,
Como somos uma fundação de caridade,
there's been quite a lot of talk about the source of the funds.
falou-se muito sobre a origem dos fundos.
I will keep that in mind, Director Go.
Vou ter isso em mente, Diretor Go.
All right, then. I'll see you around.
Tudo bem, então. Vemo-nos por aí.
Yes, sir.
Sim, senhor.
Yes.
Sim.
Oh, that's nice.
Ah, que giro.
Okay. See you.
Ok. Até à próxima.
-Goodbye. -Bye.
-Adeus.
Booked a chartered flight with Jeon Tae-su's money.
Reservei um voo fretado com o dinheiro de Jeon Tae-su.
Let's go.
Vamos.
Yes.
Sim.
The trucks are entering the premises.
Os camiões estão a entrar no local.
They've all entered the premises.
Todos entraram no local.
All right. Let's get on the flight.
Tudo bem. Vamos embarcar.
And now, our great journey begins.
E agora, começa a nossa grande viagem.
-Sand Foundation, let's do this! -Let's do this!
-Sand Foundation, vamos a isso! -Vamos a isso!
-This is almost over. -I'd like to thank the supporters…
-Está quase a acabar. -Gostaria de agradecer aos apoiantes…
Anyway, why are the supplies not here yet?
De qualquer forma, porque é que os mantimentos ainda não chegaram?
Just be patient. Luck is always on my side.
Tenha apenas paciência. A sorte está sempre do meu lado.
Can you make a finger heart?
Consegue fazer um coração de dedo?
-Sand Foundation, let's do this! -Let's do this!
-Sand Foundation, vamos a isso! -Vamos a isso!
Thank you. Okay.
Obrigado. Ok.
-Sir. -Yes.
-Senhor. -Sim.
Take a look at this.
Dê uma vista de olhos nisso.
It's here.
Está aqui.
EMERGENCY RELIEF SUPPLIES
SUPRIMENTOS DE AUXÍLIO DE EMERGÊNCIA
Wrap things up here.
Conclua as coisas aqui.
Yes, sir.
Sim, senhor.
We'll wrap up the interview here due to the flight schedule.
Terminaremos aqui a entrevista devido ao horário do voo.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
Sir.
Senhor.
Let's get on the plane.
Vamos entrar no avião.
Yes, sir.
Sim, senhor.
We should enjoy the ending of our project together.
Devíamos aproveitar o final do nosso projeto juntos.
Something feels different, don't you think?
Algo parece diferente, não acha?
Don't be distracted and keep your head in the game.
Não se distraia e mantenha a cabeça no jogo.
But…
Mas…
We pulled the money bags from the cargo hold
Tirámos as sacolas de dinheiro do porão de carga
and had them brought up.
e criou-os.
Thanks.
Obrigado.
I couldn't have done it without you two.
Eu não teria conseguido sem vocês os dois.
Thank you, sir.
Obrigado, senhor.
We can't take the credit.
Não podemos ficar com o crédito.
You were the one who gave us a chance.
Foi você que nos deu uma oportunidade.
I'll use the restroom.
Vou usar a casa de banho.
Oh, the restroom.
Ah, a casa de banho.
Thanks.
Obrigado.
EMERGENCY RELIEF SUPPLIES
SUPRIMENTOS DE AUXÍLIO DE EMERGÊNCIA
Yi-rang.
Yi-rang.
I was clear on the plan up until now, but what do we do moving forward?
O plano era claro até agora, mas o que faremos daqui para a frente?
We'll figure it out as we go.
Vamos descobrir isso à medida que avançamos.
What do you mean?
O que queres dizer?
What's that supposed to mean?
O que quer dizer?
Oh, the restroom is occupied.
Ah, a casa de banho está ocupada.
What? What are you doing?
O quê? O que estás a fazer?
What a shame.
Que pena.
-What? -It was almost perfect.
-O quê? -Foi quase perfeito.
Sir, why are you doing this?
Senhor, porque é que o senhor está a fazer isso?
KOREAN TOURIST MURDERED IN THE PHILIPPINES
TURISTA COREANA ASSASSINADA NAS FILIPINAS
CONFIRMED AS THE LOVE CHILD OF RISING AIRLINES CHAIRMAN
CONFIRMADA COMO FILHA AMOROSA DO PRESIDENTE DA Rising Airlines
How dare you try to steal my money?
Como se atreve a tentar roubar o meu dinheiro?
Oh, dear. You poor things.
Ai, meu Deus. Coitadinhos de vós.
How can you be this unlucky?
Como pode ter tanto azar?
Or maybe,
Ou talvez,
I'm just that lucky?
Tenho essa mesma sorte?
I can explain everything.
Eu posso explicar tudo.
-Sure. -Wait.
-Claro. -Espera.
-Hey, don't move. -What are you doing?
-Ei, não se mexa. -O que está a fazer?
That reminds me. No wonder you looked so familiar.
Isso faz-me lembrar. Não é de estranhar que lhe parecesse tão familiar.
But who cares about all of that now?
Mas quem se importa com tudo isto agora?
It'll all be over soon.
Tudo acabará em breve.
Please, sir.
Por favor, Sr.
-Don't do this. -Hey, don't move.
-Não faça isso. -Ei, não se mexa.
Once you wake up, this will all be behind you. Okay?
Quando acordar, tudo isto ficará para trás. Certo?
Your job and your life too.
O seu trabalho e a sua vida também.
Hold on.
Espera.
-What was that? -What's going on?
-O que foi aquilo? -O que está a acontecer?
What just happened?
O que acabou de acontecer?
Sir, are you okay?
Senhor, está bem?
We're experiencing turbulence.
Estamos a passar por turbulência.
Please be seated and fasten your seat belts.
Por favor, sentem-se e apertem os cintos de segurança.
Darn it.
Droga.
What's happening?
O que está a acontecer?
Hey, go to your seats.
Ei, vão para os vossos lugares.
Darn it!
Droga!
Hey, wake up.
Ei, acorda.
Wake up, for goodness' sake!
Acordem, por amor de Deus!
Due to engine damage and the risk of fire,
Devido a danos no motor e ao risco de incêndio,
we are unable to continue to our destination as we planned.
não podemos continuar até ao nosso destino como planeamos.
We'll attempt an emergency landing at the nearest airport.
Tentaremos uma aterragem de emergência no aeroporto mais próximo.
-Sorry for the inconvenience-- -Shut it!
-Desculpe o incómodo-- -Cale-se!
No!
Não!
Watch out! Be careful!
Cuidado! Tenha cuidado!
What is that?
O que é aquilo?
Look.
Olhar.
Huh?
Hã?
In order to ensure a safe landing, we need to lighten the aircraft.
Para garantir uma aterragem segura, precisamos de aliviar o peso da aeronave.
We kindly ask for your cooperation.
Pedimos gentilmente a sua colaboração.
Lighten the aircraft?
Aliviar o peso da aeronave?
Hey, flight attendant.
Olá, assistente de bordo.
Hey! What are you doing?
Olá! O que estás a fazer?
Sir! This is a dangerous situation, so be quiet!
Senhor! Esta é uma situação perigosa, por isso fique quieto!
Hey, don't touch mine. I said don't touch it.
Ei, não toques no meu. Eu disse para não tocar.
Hey! I made it clear.
Ei! Eu deixei claro.
Hey!
Olá!
Hey, man. Be quiet!
Ei, pá. Fica quieto!
She's only doing what's necessary.
Ela só está a fazer o que é necessário.
First Officer!
Primeiro Oficial!
Altitude loss! Cabin depressurization!
Perda de altitude! Despressurização da cabine!
Yes, sir.
Sim, senhor.
You…
Tu…
Oh my. Sir…
Oh meu Deus. Senhor…
-Don't. -Let go of me.
-Não. -Solte-me.
Don't touch my stuff!
Não toque nas minhas coisas!
Emergency exit. One, two, three.
Saída de emergência. Um, dois, três.
It's too dangerous. You can't do that.
É muito perigoso. Não pode fazer isso.
-Seriously. Don't do it! -No!
-Sério. Não faça isso! -Não!
Let go of me! No! Darn it!
Solta-me! Não! Droga!
Release the heavy cargo!
Solte a carga pesada!
Release!
Lançamento!
Hey!
Olá!
What the heck are you doing now?
O que raio está a fazer agora?
End of release!
Fim do lançamento!
-Wait… -No. Sir. Wait.
-Espere… -Não, senhor. Espere.
You dumped everything?
Largou tudo?
Thanks to everyone's cooperation, we were able to react fast.
Graças à cooperação de todos, conseguimos reagir rapidamente.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
You…
Tu…
Hi. It's dangerous. Get back to your seat.
Olá. É perigoso. Volte para o seu lugar.
Captain Kim.
Capitão Kim.
You punks. Are you out of your minds?
Os seus punks. Estão loucos?
-Gu-ho. -Yes?
-Gu-ho. -Sim?
-Yes.
-Sim.
Yi-rang's calling you.
Yi-rang está a ligar para si.
What?
O quê?
Wake up, boy. Get to work.
Acorda, miúdo. Mãos à obra.
What's going on?
O que está a acontecer?
Are you out of your mind?
Está louco?
Let go of me!
Solte-me!
Did you just dump my 50 billion?
Acabou de se livrar dos meus 50 mil milhões?
Right! That was money!
Certo! Era dinheiro!
What are you going to do? I threw it all out.
O que vai fazer? Deitei tudo fora.
What are we going to do?
O que vamos fazer?
Open it.
Abra-o.
What?
O quê?
-Grab it. -Grab it?
-Pegue nisto. -Pegue nisto?
-Okay. -Put it on.
- Certo. - Vista.
Put it on!
Vista-o!
Are you telling me to jump off this plane?
Está a dizer-me para pular deste avião?
-Of course! -Okay!
-Claro! -Ok!
Don't you dare move!
Não ouse mexer-se!
Or I'm going to kill you both!
Ou vou matar-vos aos dois!
Put this on!
Vista isso!
What? Why do I…
O quê? Porquê eu…
Hey, you take it.
Ei, tu pegas.
Put it on. What are you doing?
Vista-o. O que está a fazer?
Put it on and go find my money!
Coloque-o e vá encontrar o meu dinheiro!
I saved your sorry lives when you were barely making a living on the streets.
Eu salvei as vossas vidas miseráveis ​​quando vocês mal conseguiam sobreviver nas ruas.
I gave you a shot at a decent life,
Eu dei-te uma oportunidade de uma vida decente,
and this is how you repay me?
e é assim que me retribui?
What are you going to do?
O que vai fazer?
Are you going to jump off? Just for that?
Vai pular? Só por isso?
"Just for that?"
"Só por isso?"
You've never had this kind of money,
Nunca teve esse tipo de dinheiro,
so of course you don't get it.
então é claro que não percebeu.
-Did he jump? -My gosh!
-Ele saltou? -Meu Deus!
Close the door.
Feche a porta.
-How do I close it? -Grab that.
-Como fecho isto? -Pegue nisto.
Grab that.
Pegue nisto.
You got it.
Você entendeu.
You got it! Nice!
Isso mesmo! Fixe!
One, two, three.
Um, dois, três.
There it is.
Aí está.
There are my babies.
Aqui estão os meus bebés.
Oh, my precious babies.
Ah, os meus preciosos bebés.
My babies.
Meus bebés.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
What is this?
O que é isto?
Darn it!
Droga!
The aircraft is now safe.
A aeronave está agora segura.
Ladies and gentlemen, we'll take you safely to your destination.
Senhoras e senhores, nós levar-vos-emos em segurança ao vosso destino.
James, while we're buying time outside,
James, enquanto ganhamos tempo lá fora,
swap the money bags that are in the cargo hold.
troque as bolsas de dinheiro que estão no porão de carga.
Do you know how hard it was to switch all those money bags by myself?
Sabe o quão difícil foi trocar todas aquelas sacolas de dinheiro sozinha?
Good job. Well done.
Bom trabalho. Bem feito.
Nice acting.
Boa atuação.
Well done.
Bem feito.
Yi-rang, good work. Well done.
Yi-rang, bom trabalho. Parabéns.
Gu-ho, good job.
Vaiaa, bom trabalho.
James…
Tiago…
Oh no.
Oh não.
What is wrong with him? He's sleeping all day.
O que há de errado com ele? Ele está a dormir o dia todo.
That punk. He's so fragile.
Aquele punk. Ele é tão frágil.
Ta-da!
É isso!
Remember how I bought a winery in Burgundy, France, last month?
Lembram-se que comprei uma adega na Borgonha, França, no mês passado?
Yes.
Sim.
This champagne is from that winery.
Este champanhe é daquela adega.
Since I'm the owner, I should have a taste.
Como sou o dono, devo experimentar.
Of course you should.
Claro que sim.
How could you do that to me?
Como é que me pôde fazer isto?
Sorry. Just come and join us.
Desculpe. Venha juntar-se a nós.
-No. -Just come here.
-Não. -Vem só aqui.
-Come here!
-Vem cá!
I just don't get it.
Eu simplesmente não entendo.
Explain it to me.
Explique-me.
How much of it was real and how much of it was fake?
Quanto disso era real e quanto era falso?
It's true that James approached him disguised as a captain.
É verdade que James se aproximou dele disfarçado de capitão.
If you don't mind, can I get your business card too?
Se não se importa, pode dar-me o seu cartão de visita também?
Jeon Tae-su was way more skeptical than expected.
Jeon Tae-su estava muito mais cético do que o esperado.
It was hard to buy his trust.
Foi difícil comprar a sua confiança.
So we realized it wouldn't work out and withdrew.
Então percebemos que não iria resultar e desistimos.
TRUTH
VERDADE
From then on, it was a lie.
Daí em diante, foi mentira.
Jeon Tae-su never showed up at the cargo ship that day.
Jeon Tae-su não apareceu no navio de carga nesse dia.
So James getting assaulted and beaten up was a lie we made up.
Então, o James ter sido agredido e espancado foi uma mentira que inventámos.
FALSE
FALSO
We kept waiting for Jeon Tae-su to call us after that,
Continuamos à espera que Jeon Tae-su nos ligue depois disso,
but because he was so skeptical, he never even texted us.
mas como era tão cético, nunca nos enviou mensagem.
Change of plan.
Mudança de planos.
But as soon as we withdrew the operation,
Mas assim que retiramos a operação,
you came to our minds.
você veio à nossa mente.
Because what Jeon Tae-su wants is not trust
Porque o que Jeon Tae-su quer não é confiança
but absolute loyalty and obedience.
mas lealdade e obediência absolutas.
So that was the plan.
Portanto, esse era o plano.
You really had this all figured out from the start!
Realmente já tinha tudo planeado desde o início!
Gu-ho, pass me the truffle oil over there.
Gu-ho, passa-me aquele óleo de trufa ali.
Could you grind some Himalayan pink salt for me?
Poderia moer um pouco de sal rosa dos Himalaias para mim?
Seriously, my life is just…
A sério, a minha vida é simplesmente…
It's got a great body.
Tem um corpo ótimo.
So refreshing.
Tão refrescante.
Seriously.
A sério.
See? Absolute loyalty and obedience.
Viu? Lealdade e obediência absolutas.
That's what you embody. You were perfect for this job.
É isso que personifica. Eras perfeita para este trabalho.
You can't have this. Don't eat it.
Não pode comer isso. Não coma.
We're saying you're considerate.
Estamos a dizer que é atencioso.
-Is that so? -Yes.
-É mesmo? -Sim.
-Eat. -Thank you.
-Comer. -Obrigado.
Wait, you were going to jump off the plane.
Espera, ias saltar do avião.
What was that about?
Do que foi?
Yi-rang, I'd always known that you were crazy, but I never--
Yi-rang, sempre soube que eras louco, mas nunca...
At altitudes below 3,000 meters,
Em altitudes inferiores a 3.000 metros,
the pressure difference between the cabin and the outside isn't severe,
a diferença de pressão entre a cabine e o exterior não é grave,
so there's no risk of sudden decompression.
então não há risco de descompressão súbita.
FLIGHT ALTITUDE = 1,000 METERS
ALTITUDE DE VOO = 1.000 METROS
So as long as we didn't climb any higher...
Assim, enquanto não subíssemos mais alto...
I had already run the numbers.
Eu já tinha feito as contas.
Hey, still, that was wrong. You know?
Ei, ainda assim, isso estava errado. Sabia?
I'm serious.
Estou a falar a sério.
James, it must've been so easy for you.
Tiago, deve ter sido muito fácil para si.
What?
O quê?
When I was fighting for my life,
Quando estava a lutar pela minha vida,
you were just lying on the hospital bed all comfortable, just killing time.
estavas deitado na cama do hospital , todo confortável, só a matar o tempo.
What are you talking about? I was really busy.
Do que é que está a falar? Eu estava muito ocupado.
I was always by your side.
Estive sempre ao seu lado.
What are you talking about?
O que é que está a falar?
This isn't an art piece, so just take the pictures.
Esta não é uma obra de arte, por isso tire apenas fotografias.
You're not filming a movie.
Não está a filmar um filme.
He left.
Ele foi-se embora.
-Did he leave? -Yes.
-Ele foi-se embora? -Sim.
Salute. Thank you, sir.
Saudação. Obrigado, senhor.
Okay, bye.
Ok, tchau.
Gosh.
Poxa.
Why did they have to make it so tight? I told them this wasn't necessary.
Porque é que tiveram que apertar tanto? Eu disse que não era necessário.
I don't have time for this.
Não tenho tempo para isso.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTOR GENERAL
PROCURADOR-GERAL DO DISTRITO CENTRAL DE SEUL
I can't feel my arm.
Não consigo sentir o meu braço.
But I'm so busy.
Mas estou muito ocupado.
Oh, be quiet.
Ah, fique quieto.
Where are you going?
Onde vai?
I'm so sick of you.
Estou tão farto de ti.
I've had enough. Don't try to find me!
Já chega. Não tente encontrar-me!
I think he's really sick of us this time. I can feel it.
Acho que ele está mesmo farto de nós desta vez. Dá para sentir.
That hurts! Yi-rang. James.
Isso dói! Yi-rang. Tiago.
What's up, Ray-bang?
E aí, Ray-bang?
Help me. What's he doing?
Ajudem-me. O que está ele a fazer?
You didn't have to bring anything.
Não precisava de trazer nada.
Salute.
Saudação.
Hello. Good work, everyone.
Olá. Bom trabalho a todos.
Yes. Good work.
Sim. Bom trabalho.
You were from…
Você era de…
When did this happen? Huh?
Quando é que isso aconteceu? Hã?
He's my junior from the Marine Corps. He happened to be working for Jeon Tae-su.
É meu aluno do Corpo de Fuzileiros. Por acaso, estava a trabalhar para Jeon Tae-su.
So I scouted him immediately.
Então, observei-o imediatamente.
Mr. Ray-Bang here brought Mr. Mustache, who used to work in film,
O Sr. Ray-Bang trouxe aqui o Sr. Mustache, que trabalhava em cinema,
and that's how we got our secret agents.
e foi assim que conseguimos os nossos agentes secretos.
Okay.
Ok.
Well done.
Bem feito.
Here, this is for you,
Aqui, isto é para si,
and this is for Mr. Mustache.
e isto é para o Sr. Bigode.
Thank you, sir. I will continue to do my best.
Obrigado, senhor. Continuarei a dar o meu melhor.
Thank you. Have a seat.
Obrigado. Sente-se.
This is yours, Gu-ho.
Isto é teu, Gu-ho.
What happened to the rest?
O que aconteceu ao resto?
Do you know how much it costs to charter a plane?
Sabe quanto custa fretar um avião?
We also had to send the relief supplies.
Também tivemos de enviar mantimentos de socorro.
Wait. Be quiet.
Espere. Fique quieto.
We recently reported that Nazareth,
Recentemente noticiámos que a Nazaré,
a home that supports youth in becoming independent,
uma casa que apoia os jovens na busca da independência,
was at risk of being shut down due to misunderstandings and rumors.
corria o risco de ser encerrado devido a mal-entendidos e rumores.
However, two days ago, an anonymous donor made a significant contribution,
No entanto, há dois dias, um doador anónimo deu um contributo significativo,
and a new center is set to be built.
e um novo centro está prestes a ser construído.
A FEW DAYS AGO
HÁ ALGUNS DIAS
LET THIS BE USED TO NURTURE THE FUTURE
LET THIS BE USED TO NURTURE THE FUTURE
Sister.
Sister.
Sister!
Sister!
By the Lord's grace,
By the Lord's grace,
an anonymous brother who shares our spirit
an anonymous brother who shares our spirit
has bestowed upon us a profound blessing.
has bestowed upon us a profound blessing.
So that's where it went?
So that's where it went?
Give them this too. Give it to them.
Give them this too. Give it to them.
Whatever. You deserve to keep it.
Whatever. You deserve to keep it.
We're not running a charity here.
We're not running a charity here.
He's right. Gu-ho.
He's right. Gu-ho.
Get yourself some snacks with your little money.
Get yourself some snacks with your little money.
Up next.
Up next.
Jeon Tae-su, chairman of the Sand Foundation,
Jeon Tae-su, chairman of the Sand Foundation,
is under arrest for child abuse and aggravated unlawful confinement.
is under arrest for child abuse and aggravated unlawful confinement.
Jeon Tae-su.
Jeon Tae-su.
Police have discovered that former Chairman Jeon
Police have discovered that former Chairman Jeon
subjected children to prolonged abuse and unlawful confinement
subjected children to prolonged abuse and unlawful confinement
within the welfare center he ran.
within the welfare center he ran.
They will conduct an investigation…
They will conduct an investigation…
Yi-rang.
Yi-rang.
Why did you choose Jeon Tae-su of all people?
Why did you choose Jeon Tae-su of all people?
He seemed different from the usual dirty laundry we've handled.
He seemed different from the usual dirty laundry we've handled.
She's sleeping.
She's sleeping.
Well, that was fast. Let's go.
Well, that was fast. Let's go.
-Okay. -Follow me.
-Okay. -Follow me.
25 YEARS AGO
25 YEARS AGO
Too bad. I won again.
Too bad. I won again.
Since you lost, you need to get punished.
Since you lost, you need to get punished.
It's unfair.
It's unfair.
What's unfair?
What's unfair?
Oh, are you saying you keep losing
Oh, are you saying you keep losing
because they scare you?
because they scare you?
No. I'm just way younger than you.
No. I'm just way younger than you.
But you're smarter than I am.
But you're smarter than I am.
What if I can't outthink all that life experience you have?
What if I can't outthink all that life experience you have?
And what if…
And what if…
And I'm just throwing it out there.
And I'm just throwing it out there.
But you could be smarter than I am.
But you could be smarter than I am.
That makes sense.
That makes sense.
Fine. Then we'll play the game you want.
Fine. Then we'll play the game you want.
What do you want to play?
What do you want to play?
How about hide-and-seek?
How about hide-and-seek?
Sure.
Claro.
Go.
Go.
Hide tight, I can see your hair
Hide tight, I can see your hair
I mean, is this really necessary?
I mean, is this really necessary?
Found you.
Found you.
ANY WORLD THEME PARK KIDNAP CASE, MYUNG GU-HO, AGE 28
ANY WORLD THEME PARK KIDNAP CASE, MYUNG GU-HO, AGE 28
An art critic well-versed in all forms of artistic expression
An art critic well-versed in all forms of artistic expression
and a major player in the art business world.
and a major player in the art business world.
Then, today, will we get to see an authentic masterpiece?
Then, today, will we get to see an authentic masterpiece?
All right. Let's find out who he is.
All right. Let's find out who he is.
Come to the gallery with the paintings.
Come to the gallery with the paintings.
That crazy…
That crazy…
He's a piece of trash
He's a piece of trash
who takes advantage of his status to go after women.
who takes advantage of his status to go after women.
James, wait. Did we get caught?
James, wait. Did we get caught?
I'm the Head of Purchasing for Wonderby Asia. Olivia Kim.
I'm the Head of Purchasing for Wonderby Asia. Olivia Kim.
We'll dangle the bait using Mr. Famous' most powerful memories.
We'll dangle the bait using Mr. Famous' most powerful memories.
Jeez!
Jeez!
What's wrong? What happened?
O que se passou? O que aconteceu?
May I ask when you arrived in Korea?
May I ask when you arrived in Korea?
You must have met Soul Auction's legal team manager.
You must have met Soul Auction's legal team manager.
Don't worry.
Don't worry.
What we need right now is the perfect pushover.
What we need right now is the perfect pushover.